{"data":[{"question":"Have you got the ticket for the baseball game yet? \"Not yet, and I ___ to get it for the last two days.\"","a":"will be trying","b":"will have been trying","c":"have been trying","d":"had tried","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect continous: We use the Present Perfect Continuous to show that something started in the past and has continued up until now (for the last two days)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It's the second time you _________ late for the class this week.","a":"are","b":"were","c":"have been","d":"had been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect: You can use the Present Perfect to describe your experience (the first time, the second time..).","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Hardly _________ they _________ to work when the machines didn't work.","a":"did, start","b":"had, started","c":"were, starting","d":"have, started","answer":"2","explain":"\n-When telling a story in the past time, if an event quickly follows another, these adverbials and partial inversion is used to express the first event. In the inverted clause usually past perfect is used","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"___ three years since the two sisters began learning French.","a":"It is","b":"They have been","c":"There are","d":"It was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense with dummy subject \"it\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"That old woman ___ the street when she was hit by a drunken driver.","a":"had just crossed","b":"was just crossing","c":"was just crossed","d":"just crossed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted (when she was hit...)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I am sorry, sir, your digital camera isn't ready yet. It ___.","a":"hasn't repaired","b":"is repaired","c":"has been repaired","d":"is being repaired","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Present continous: express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I _________ such an horrible story before.","a":"had never read","b":"have never read","c":"was never reading","d":"will never read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: use the Present Perfect to describe your experience","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"How _________ on with your new job these days? \"Not bad.\"","a":"did you get","b":"have you got","c":"have you been getting","d":"are you getting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Present continous: we use the Present Continuous to say that we are in the process of doing a longer action which is in progress; however, we might not be doing it at this exact second","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"More than 50 people ___ in traffic accidents over the past four months.","a":"have been killed","b":"were killed","c":"killed","d":"are killed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice\n- Present perfect: We often use the Present Perfect to talk about change that has happened over a period of time\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Helen has _________ for one week.","a":"been soon learning the sewing","b":"been soon learning to sew","c":"soon learned the sewing","d":"been soon learning sewing","answer":"2","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}